careersingear.com 2019-05-23

# Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy - DAC

This Privacy Policy was last updated as of October 15, 2018.

This Privacy Policy is applicable to those websites owned or controlled by Randall-Reilly, LLC that display or link to this Privacy Policy (the “ _Sites_ ”). This Privacy Policy explains what information is collected from you and other users of the Sites and how we use, disclose and secure such information, including personally identifiable information.

**Application Submission; Releases**

By submitting an application you certify that you personally completed such application and that all of the information is true and correct. Your submission of an application constitutes:

  * your request and authorization for each of the potential employers and their agents and contractors that receive your application (collectively, the “Carrier Companies”) to cause to be conducted, at any time, an investigation of your background for employment purposes, which may include, but is not limited to, any information relating to your character, general reputation, personal characteristics, mode of living, criminal history, past work experience, educational background, alcohol or drug test results (including failure to submit to an alcohol or drug test) or any other information about you which may reflect upon your potential for employment, as gathered from any individual, organization, entity, agency, or other source which may have knowledge concerning any such items of information; and
  * your representation that you have completed your application of your own free will and that you will hold harmless of all liability all companies, agents and associated parties for the use of your application.

As part of consideration of your application, the U.S. Department of Transportation requires the Carrier Companies to investigate your employment background. As part of this investigation, one or more Carrier Companies may obtain consumer reports about you from consumer reporting agencies HireRight/DAC, as well as obtaining information about your driving record from the Federal Motor Carrier Safety Administration (FMCSA) and/or the Pre-employment Screening Program (PSP). Any decision that a Carrier Company may make not to hire you based on information contained in your consumer reports will be such company’s decision alone. HireRight/DAC does not make any decisions concerning your employment with any Carrier Company and will not know the specific reasons why they may decide not to hire you. In the event you are not hired based on information contained in your consumer reports, the companies themselves will tell you. We also advise you of your right to obtain a free copy of the consumer report from HireRight/DAC and your right to dispute the accuracy or completeness of your report. Your consent for any Carrier Company to obtain the report from HireRight/DAC is required. Although you have a right to withhold your consent, the Carrier Companies will not consider your application if you withhold your consent.

By submitting your application, you authorize each of the Carrier Companies and their agents or contractors to obtain one or more reports regarding your driving and safety inspection history from the FMCSA. Any decision that any Carrier Company may make not to hire you based on information contained in your FMCSA reports will be its decision alone. By submitting your application, you also:

  * authorize each Carrier Company and their agents or contractors to access the FMCSA PSP system to seek information regarding your commercial driving safety record and information regarding your safety inspection history;
  * acknowledge that you understand that you are consenting to the release of safety performance information including crash data from the previous five (5) years and inspection history from the previous three (3) years;
  * acknowledge that you understand that this release of information may assist Carrier Companies in making a determination regarding your suitability as an employee; and
  * acknowledge that you understand that neither the Carrier Companies nor the FMCSA contractor supplying the crash and safety information have the capability to correct any safety data that appears to be incorrect. You may challenge the accuracy of the data by submitting a request to [https://dataqs.fmcsa.dot.gov](https://dataqs.fmcsa.dot.gov/). If you are challenging crash or inspection information reported by a State, FMCSA cannot change or correct this data and your request will be forwarded by the DataQs system to the appropriate State for adjudication.

### Non-personally Identifiable Information

_Navigational Information_  
We may collect and use non-personally identifiable information and data from you when you are visiting the Sites through the standard operation of our Internet servers. Non-personally identifiable information collected from you may include user Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and version, domain names, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, click stream data and anonymous statistical data regarding your use of the Sites. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify particular visitors to the Sites. We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the Sites, to track users’ movements around the Sites and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

_Cookies_  
To better understand what you do while on the Sites and to provide you with a more personalized experience on the Sites, we also collect information through the use of a browser feature known as a “cookie” (also known as a “browser cookie”). Cookies are small text files stored on your computer by your web browser that a website can use to recognize you as a repeat user, facilitate your ongoing access to, use of and navigation within the Sites, allow the Sites to track your usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow us to make content improvements, personalize your online experience and provide you with targeted offers and advertising. Cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If you do not want information collected from you through our use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with certain features available on the Site.  For additional information on your ability to opt-out of targeted offers and advertising, please see the “ _Online Behavioral Advertising_ ” section of our policy provided below.

_Flash Cookies_

Local stored objects (also known as “Flash cookies”) are text files commonly used in website advertisements and videos.  Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.  Certain features of the Sites may use Flash cookies to collect and store your preferences or display content based on what you view on the Sites to personalize your experience.  Our advertisers and third-party service providers may also use Flash cookies to collect and store information.  Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data stored and the method by which it is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies.  Please visit [Macromedia Flash Player Help](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager02.html) for more information on disabling Flash cookies.  If you disable Flash cookies, you may not have access to many features that make your experience on the Sites efficient and some of the services offered on the Sites may not function properly.

_Clear GIFS_  
We also employ a software technology called “clear gifs” (also known as “web beacons,” “pixel tags” or “web bugs”) that helps us better manage content on our Sites by providing us feedback as to what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on a website page, web-based document or email message and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to confirm receipt of, and response to, our emails, including those that you forward to other recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the “Opt-out” section below.

_Association with Personally Identifiable Information_  
We may associate your online navigational information and transactional information gathered by cookies and clear gifs to your personally identifiable information. We associate this information only for our purposes, to deliver services and products to you, to improve our business and to market our products and services through email, mobile advertising, direct mail and other media. The association of navigational information, cookies, clear gifs and personally identifiable information results in a more personalized experience on the Sites that is tailored to your interests.

### Personally Identifiable Information

_Collection and Supplementation_  
We collect personally identifiable information about you when you specifically and knowingly provide such information voluntarily on the Sites, including, but not limited to, during the following interactions: (1) when you register on a Site and when you later log-on with your user name and password; (2) when you sign-up to subscribe to a service, publication or newsletter, or ask to be added to our mailing lists; (3) when you place an order for products or services; (4) when you answer questions or otherwise provide feedback in response to inquiries on a Site or in an online survey; (5) when you participate in a sweepstakes, contest or other promotional offer; and (6) when you submit comments, messages, suggestions or other content on a Site’s public forum section or directly to RRPC.

In each of the instances above, we typically ask for some or all of the following information: your full name, email address, telephone number, mobile phone number, physical mailing address, credit card number, purchase and ordering information, demographic and product preference information, any applicable user identification number or password that we may require, as well as other similar information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. On occasion, we may ask for additional information to enable us to provide you with access to and use of certain other information, materials and services.

We may merge your information collected on the Sites with similar data obtained from third parties. We may use this enhanced personally identifiable information to better target our advertising and to notify you of special offers, updated information and new products and services in which we think you would be interested.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about a Site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit the Site, including any personalized message you provide. We store this information for the purpose of sending relevant emails to your friend, tracking the success of our referral program and further personalizing your and your friend’s experience on the Sites. Your friend may contact our Information Privacy Manager at the address and email set forth below to request that we remove this information from our database.

_Use and Disclosure_  
The personally identifiable information you provide to us when using the Sites may be used to provide our products and services to you, to enhance your experience at the Sites, and, if applicable, to process your orders and enhance your experience as a purchaser or subscriber to our products and services.

We may from time to time use your personally identifiable information to provide promotional communications that we think may be of interest to you, including faxes and email to notify you of our special offers and products and services as well as advertising from us or unaffiliated third parties. It is also possible that we may rent, sell or otherwise transfer your basic contact and product preference information to unaffiliated third parties who we think may offer services and products of interest to you. At any time, you can contact our Information Privacy Manager at the address and email set forth below to request that we not provide you with promotional communications or share your basic contact and product preference information with unaffiliated third parties.

We may employ independent contractors, vendors and suppliers (collectively, “ _Outside Contractors_ ”) to support our services and products and the Sites, such as providing credit card processing and fraud screening, order fulfillment and shipment, mailing or electronic delivery of our publications and other materials, hosting, monitoring and maintaining the Sites, administering or monitoring emails, managing sweepstakes or contests, analyzing trends and our visitors’ preferences, compiling anonymous statistics about our visitors, developing applications for the Sites and providing general consulting services. These Outside Contractors may sometimes have limited access to information collected from you, including your personally identifiable information, in the course of providing products or services to us. Access to your personally identifiable information by these Outside Contractors is limited to the information we determine, in our sole discretion, to be reasonably necessary in order for these Outside Contractors to perform their function for us. While we will seek to require any Outside Contractors to protect the privacy of your personally identifiable information under a policy at least as restrictive as this Privacy Policy and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of Outside Contractors.

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a merger, acquisition by another company or sale or other transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets (including our associated customer lists containing your personal information).

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with governmental investigations or proceedings or a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. We have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to adequately safeguard and secure the information we collect on the Sites from unauthorized access.

Notwithstanding our commitment to protect your information, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. Additionally, there also is some risk our security systems could be circumvented or breached. As a result, while we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. If you have any questions regarding the security on our Sites you can contact our Information Privacy Manager at the address and email set forth below.

### Online Behavioral Advertising

As noted in the “Non-personally Identifiable Information” section of this policy, we collect certain information through the use of navigational information and cookies in order to provide you a more customized experience on our Sites. This information may also be used by our Outside Contractors to customize certain of the advertisements that you see on our Sites and other websites based on your online behaviors and interests and to predict your interest in future advertisements through an advertising practice called online behavioral advertising (“OBA”).  We invite you to learn more about OBA at <http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/>.

At any time, you may visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> and elect to opt-out of the OBA provided by those of our Outside Contractors which participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (the “DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program.  If you choose to opt out of OBA, you will still see same number of advertisements on our Sites as before, but such advertisements may not be as relevant to you. Opting-out of OBA is cookie-based and will only affect the specific computer and browser on which the opt-out is applied. Deleting your browser cookies can remove your opt-out choices and may require you to opt-out again.  Please note that we are not affiliated with the DAA and are not responsible for the failure by DAA or any of its participating companies to honor your OBA opt-out request.

### Opt-out

As noted above, you may at any time opt-out of receiving promotional communications from us and/or request that we discontinue providing any of your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties by contacting our Information Privacy Manager at **[webmaster@rrpub.com](mailto:webmaster@rrpub.com) **or the physical address set forth below. Please note that if you decide to opt-out of receiving promotional information or request that we discontinue providing your basic contact information, your change in preference will only affect future contacts; if the information already has been provided to third parties, they may continue to use it.

Even if you choose to opt-out, we reserve the right to contact you as necessary in our sole discretion regarding any request you have made for our services or products and changes to this Privacy Policy and also to use, transfer, sell and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing the Sites’ usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

### Correcting Information

You are responsible for providing accurate information when making purchases, registering with any portion of any Site that requires registration, or performing other functions that might require you to submit personally identifiable information to the Sites. If you wish to correct any personally identifiable information you have provided to us, you may do so by contacting our Information Privacy Manager at the address and email set forth below.

### Links and Advertising

From time to time, the Sites may contain hyperlinks (“ _Links_ ”) to third party websites as well as banner advertising and sponsorships operated by or referring to third parties and their goods and services (“ _Advertising_ ”). Such Links and Advertising are for your reference only, and we neither control the privacy policies of such linked or advertised websites nor are we liable or responsible in any way for the use of any personally identifiable information that you may provide such sites. We recommend that you remain aware when you leave the Sites and review the terms of use and privacy policies of each and every linked website.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information in an email or other communications with any third party listed on the Sites or in other materials, that information, along with any other information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and correlated and used by such third parties and may result in your receiving unsolicited messages from other persons. Such collection, correlation, use and messages are beyond our control.

### Comment Sections/Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms

We allow users to share information in certain comment sections, bulletin boards and in chat rooms. Any personally identifiable information that you submit in a comment section, bulletin board or chat room can be read, collected and used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information that you choose to submit in these forums and none of the limitations in our Privacy Policy apply to any such personally identifiable information.

### How To Contact Us

If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please write or e-mail us at the following address:

**Mailing Address:**  
Randall-Reilly, LLC  
Attn: Information Privacy Manager  
3200 Rice Mine Road  
Tuscaloosa, AL 35406  
E-mail: **webmaster@rrpub.com**

### Changes To The Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by notifying users by prominently posting a notice on the Sites or by contacting you through electronic mail or other means. Your continued use of any Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of any changes.

### What If You Do Not Agree To The Terms Of This Privacy Policy?

As a subscriber to a Site, or otherwise by using any Site, you signify that you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not make any use of any of the Sites.
